<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0"
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
  xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/XDOC/2.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/xdoc-2.0.xsd">

  <properties>
    <title>Beigesoft ORM specification version #2</title>
  </properties>

  <body>

    <!-- The body of the document contains a number of sections -->
    <section name="Specification Beige-ORM version #1">
      <p>It use Reflection API to generate SQL queries (DDL and DML).</p>
      <p>It use standard Beige-Settings to describe ORM configuration with standard Properties XML.
      All <b>current</b> configuration files are located in <b>beige-orm</b> folder.</p>
      RDBMS specific configuration files saved in <b>beige-orm/[RDBMSname]</b> folder, e.g. <b>beige-orm/sqlite</b>.
      <p>DDL and SQL queries generated according simple SQL table descriptor that is assigned for every persistable class.</p>
      <p>SQL descriptors a filled by Beige-Settings with XML files and programmatically.</p>

      <h4>SQL descriptor TableSql</h4>
      <p>Consist of:
        <ul>
          <li>Map[fieldName-FieldSql] - fields map there fieldName same as in the class, e.g. "itsName"</li>
          <li>versionAlgorithm - optimistic locking version algorithm. 0 - autoincrement, 1 - date changed.</li>
          <li>constraint - table all CONSTRAINTs e.g. PRIMARY KEY ("id"), FOREIGN KEY.....</li>
          <li>idName - ID name (field primary non-complex key) e.g. "itsId" (complex is always null!!!).</li>
          <li>idDefinitionForeign - ID SQL definition for foreign key non-complex (complex is always null!!!),
          e.g. Customer.itsId has SQL type "bigserial primary key", but Invoice.Customer has definition "bigint".</li>
          <li>isFullDefinedInXml - if this table doesn't need to farther define by program.</li>
        </ul>
      </p>
      
      <h4>SQL descriptor FieldSql</h4>
      <p>Consist of:
        <ul>
          <li>definition - DDL string e.g. "INTEGER NOT NULL"</li>
          <li>foreignEntity - simple class name o foreign (owned) entity e.g. for itsDepartment "Department".
          It used to resolve LEFT JOIN in SELECT statement.</li>
        </ul>
      </p>
      
      <h4>Tables descriptor.</h4>
      <p>This is map ["EntitySimpleName - TableSql"]</p>
        
      <h4>Base configuration file <b>persistance-[RDBMS].xml</b> consist of:</h4>
      <p>useSubFolder - <b>sqlite</b> | <b>postgresql</b> | <b>h2</b>. It used as name of directory that contains RDBMS specific configuration files.</p>
      <p>classes - array of classes names(name include package same as getClass().getCanonicalName()) that
      represent persistable models.</p>
      <p>settingsKeysForClases - "idName, idDefinitionForeign, constraintAdd, constraint, isFullDefinedInXml, excludeFields", they are reserved settings, so don't change them.</p>
      <p>settingsKeysForFields - "definition, isNullable, foreignEntity", they are reserved settings, so don't change them.</p>
      <p>excludeFields - array of non-persistable fields names for all classes, e.g. <b>isNew</b>.</p>
      
      <h4>Application settings file <b>[RDBMS]/app-settings.xml</b> consist of:</h4>
      <p>jdbcDriverClass - SQL driver class name.</p>
      <p>databaseUrl - a database url of the form jdbc:subprotocol:subname.</p>
      <p>userName - RDBMS user name.</p>
      <p>userPassword - RDBMS user password.</p>
      <p>checkTableExist - SQL select statment what return if table exist e.g. "select * from SQLITE_MASTER where TBL_NAME=':tableName';".</p>
      <p>H2 required full path of database file e.g. <b>jdbc:h2:~/beigeaccountingtest</b> is in linux "home" path.
      For multiplatform purpose there is non-standard word <b>#currentDir#</b> that point to current working directory = System.getProperty("user.dir").
      So JDBC URL will be <b>jdbc:h2:#currentDir#beigeaccountingtest</b> .Also word <b>#currentParentDir#</b> is point to System.getProperty("user.dir").
      So testing databases for JUnit used <b>#currentParentDir#</b> and will be at [sourceBeigeErp/]</p>

      <h4>Common rules to generate DDL and SQL statements for persistable models.</h4>
      <p>ALTER TABLE not supported, so just run it manually.</p>
      <p>SQL92 problemable standard says that tables and fields names are either without quotes case insensitive or in quotes case sensitive
      <a href="https://pubs.vmware.com/vfabric5/index.jsp?topic=/com.vmware.vfabric.sqlfire.1.0/reference/language_ref/sql_identifiers.html">SQL identifiers</a>. 
      But not all database services accept names with quotes e.g. Jetty JDBC realm.
      H2, Oracle treated field name without quotes itsId as ITSID, but Postgresql as itsid.
      So Beige ORM used upper case names. To make SQL queries more redable SQL words are in lower case.
      E.g. <b>create table USERJETTY (ITSID bigserial primary key, ITSNAME text not null).</b>.
      I recommend very friendly and usefull H2 HTML based console utility. With it you can quickly make huge SQL query as fast as with
      a visual SQL query builder. It insert upper case table and field name in query string when you click on a table or a field.
      </p>
      <p>It would be better if SQL identifier standard was as Java one.
        In that case SQL queries (generated) will be more readable, e.g. "SELECT itsName FROM InvItem WHERE itsId=2;".
      </p>
      <p>Table name is class simple name in UPPER CASE letters.</p>
      <p>Table field name is class field name in UPPER CASE letters.</p>
      <p>Consequently all persistable models must have unique simple class name and their fields used prefix "its" to
      prevent names collision.</p>
      <p>But in XML files and in descriptors fields names are same as in class
      cause use Java reflection API.</p>

      <p>For unification purpose RDBMS types are Sqlite-oriented i.e. 
      <b>java.util.Date</b> stored as <b>Long</b> and <b>Boolean</b> stored as <b>Integer</b>
       in all RDBMS</p>
            
      <h4>Reveal column definition automatically.</h4>
      <p>Beige-Settings makes it from XML files:
        <ul>
          <li>file <b>[RDBMS]/javaTypeToFs/definition.xml</b>.
          It contains simple set of Java types and corresponded RDBMS types. 
          E.g. for SQlite entries like - "java.lang.Integer" - "INTEGER", "java.util.Date" - "INTEGER"</li>
          <li>file <b>[RDBMS]/fieldNameJavaTypeToFs/[fieldName]definition.xml</b>.
          It contains set of Java types and corresponded RDBMS types. 
          E.g. for primary key "itsId" on SQlite - "java.lang.Integer" - "integer not null primary key autoincrement"</li>
          <li>file <b>[RDBMS]/fieldNameToFs/definition.xml</b>.
          It contains set of field names corresponded RDBMS types. 
          E.g. "itsName" - "string not null", "itsDate" - "integer not null"</li>
        </ul>
      </p>

      <h4>Reveal DDL primary ID automatically.</h4>
      <p>ID always defined with XML. See Beige-Accounting WarehouseRest for complex ID example.</p>

      <h4>Reveal DDL for foreign ID automatically.</h4>
      <p>Foreign (owned) entity revials automatically along with restriction foreign key. E.g. column "itsDepartment" - "integer"
      will be same tape as primapy key entity "Department". Also constraint "foreign key (ITSDEPARTMENT)
      references DEPARTMENT (ITSID)" will be added.</p>
      <p>If field type simple name exist in tablesMap that means it's foreign entity.
      To make such field NOT NULL add its setting isNullable = false. Class settings idName and idDefinitionForeign must be filled.</p>
      
      <h4>Create tables</h4>
      <p>Tables will be created automatically if no exist according app setting <b>checkTableExist</b>.</p>
      <p>This is simple SELECT statement that has parameter <b>:tableName</b> that will be replaced by real table name.
      If query return 0 records - table not exist.</p>
            
      <h4>DML queries.</h4>
      <p>Update/Insert queries are maked in usual way.</p>
      <p>Select never retrieve owned items set (these are Many to One composition e.g. invoice's lines). 
      But SELECT always retrieve owned entities (1st level) (that is One to One aggregation e.g. invoice's organization).
      E.g. retrieved SalesInvoice already has retrieved property Customer, but Customer has 2-d level entity
      PreferCurrency only ID. So to retrieve full model Customer->PreferCurrency you should make 2-nd query (invoke ORM retrieve entity by ID).</p>
      <p>Entities with complex ID are inserted in usual way, but they retrieved and updated with manually WHERE clause. 
      See Beige-Accounting WarehouseRest in SrvPurchaseInvoiceLine for example</p>

      <h5>Database Info persistable model</h5>
      <p>Persistable model org.beigesoft.persistable.DatabaseInfo consist of:
        <ul>
          <li>databaseId - Integer, not null primary key and database ID</li>
          <li>databaseVersion - Integer, not null database version</li>
          <li>description - String</li>
        </ul>
        This is only row existed in table. If database has been just created then only entry DatabaseInfo
        will be inserted, databaseId is randomly generated, databaseVersion=1 of course, description="a database".
        You can change database description (only!!!) by hand.
      </p>

      <h4>Creating tables.</h4>
      <p>You have to invoke method ASrvOrm.initializeDatabase() at ORM start time. Beige-ORM will create tables that not existed.
      It never alter tables so you have to make script upgrade_[new_version].sql script. If all tables has been created
      then insert.sql will be invoked if it exist.</p>
      
      <h4>Upgrade database.</h4>
      <p>The most task of upgrade do not only upgrade tables definition, they also do inserts and update data, triggers, views.
        So database must has version. When it's need to upgrade database then make script upgrade_[new version].sql
        and BeigeORM start it in single transaction. This script should update database version itself.
      </p>

      <h4>Transaction management</h4>
      <p>There is two approaches to prevent dirty read:
        <ol>
          <li>Locking table or row. Not good for performance.</li>
          <li>Dirty check - it's calling optimistic locking</li>
        </ol>
        E.g. Postgresql for <b>Repeatable read</b> isolation mode block table to prevent changing.
        But Postgresql for <b>Serializable</b> mode use checking (not exactly locking).
        During INSERT/UPDATE any record is locked.
        Performance depends of locking implementation in concrete RDBMS.
        BeigeERP is designed for high-performance. It's time to go from abstraction to concrete business logic.
        Use <b>Read uncommitted</b> level and <b>check version</b> for an Invoice gives same result as <b>repeatable read</b>. 
        Maintenance <b>theRest</b> of a good with checking <b>CHECK theRest >= 0</b>
        will not fail transaction if theRest has changed by another transaction but it still enought.
        It's reliable and cheap way that reqired only <p>Read uncommitted</p> level.
        Calculation Cost of Goods Sold is involving many records to be read. Any way there is no difference
        data has been changed during calculation or after. So just maintain <b>invoicesVersion</b> that increments each time that
        an invoice has inserted or updated (so do for receipt and other influencing data) and recalculate COGS when it need.
        So use custom <b>dirty check</b> and <b>Read uncommitted</b> level is reliable way that gives performance adventages.
      </p>
      <p>A RDBMS may not implements all 4 isolation modes.
        Postgresql treated <b>read uncommited</b> as <b>read commited</b>.
        Sqlite implements only <b>serializable</b> and <b>read uncommited</b>.
      </p>
      
      <h4>Optimistic locking by "version check".</h4>
      <p>Entity should has <b>itsVersion</b> filed of type <b>Long</b>.</p>
      <p>Version algorithms:
        <ol>
          <li>Auto-increment</li>
          <li>Time changed</li>
        </ol>
        Class setting "versionAlgorithm" is used to set field <b>versionAlgorithm</b> in <b>org.beigesoft.orm.model.TableSql</b> 
      </p>

      <p>
        Many ORM use "Lazy initialization" by default that required "transaction per request/view". But "Lazy" means 
        many SQL requests, that's not good for performance. Also holding connection during whole request is not good for performance.
        Beige-ORM retrieve almost full model through 2 level. E.g. an retrieved Invoice has already retrieved Customer(1st level),
        but in this Customer DefaultCurrency(2-nd level) has only ID. Beige-ORM never retrieved owned entities-list, e.g. InvoiceLines.
        So it's take 2 SQL queries to retrieve model Invoice. 
        Standard "Lazy configured" ORM takes more SQL requests to retrieve such model.
        User can works with owned entities-list as well as with standard entities-list.
        I.e. user can filter and order it. It's useful for huge owned list, e.g. a warehouse can has hundreds places.
        Bean Managed Transactions (code inside business service) actually more flexable then CMT cause you can change
        business service with new logic by invoking simple setter for it during runtime.
      </p>
            
      <h5>Exceptions throw ExceptionWithCode:</h5>
      <ul>
        <li>1000 - not_yet_implemented</li>
        <li>1001 - Something goes wrong, e.g. attempt to update entity with complex ID by update without where that not yet supported</li>
        <li>1002 - Configuration mistake</li>
        <li>1151 - dirty_read</li>
        <li>1152 - exception update/insert It should be 1 row updated/inserted but it was...</li>
        <li>1153 - BAD_PARAMS bad parameters e.g. isolation level</li>
        <li>1154 - SQL_EXEC_ERROR SQL exception</li>
      </ul>
    </section>


  </body>

</document>
